Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Deindustrialization and the two tier society: challenges for an industrial polic, 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
    Author: Owen Bieber
  - Item 4: The polarization of America, 1986; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
    Author: Lawrence R. Mishel; Owen Bieber
  - Item 5: By intelligence and by faith, 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Clean democratic trade unions, 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Labor, big business, and inflation, 1958; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Industrial Union Dept. Research Section.
  - Item 8: Coordinated bargaining: labors new approach to effective contract negotiations., Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Toward a new foreign policy, 1989; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
    Author: Lane Kirkland
  - Item 10: Labor and antitrust, 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from IUD Digest. Second copy
  - Item 11: The two faces of G.E., 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: More than wages, 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: The outlook for labor and social legislation by John F. Kennedy, 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Our greatest challenge, 1957; Publication (Box 424, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor, big business, and inflation., 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Good for business; an employer views the union shop, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
    Notes: An addressat second annual Industrial Relations Conference of the Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO, New York, N.Y., June 17, 1958. 2 copies
  - Item 3: Respect for our elders; financing health care for our senior citizens., 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The American character, 1964; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
    Author: J. William Fulbright
  - Item 5: The southern labor story, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Union shop and the public welfare, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Industrial Union Dept. Industrial Relations Conference (2nd: 1958: New York, N.Y.)
    Notes: Proceedings of the 2nd annual industrial relations conference, Industrial Union Dept. AFL-CIO, May 17 and 18, 1958, New York, N.Y.
  - Item 7: Our stake in human rights, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The Industrial Union Department, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: More than wages, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Challenge of 1958, Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
    Author: Hubert H. Humphrey
    Notes: Speech.
  - Item 11: Justice when it counts most, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 425, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Remarks of Albert Whitehouseat the Conference on Industrial Engineering Problems, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 2)
    Author: Albert Whitehouse
  - Item 2: article - What's lacking in labor education, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 2)
    Author: Russ Allen
  - Item 3: IUD Fact sheet, 1957; Publication (Box 425, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.8
  - Item 4: Union research and technical services in the United States, 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 2)
    Author: Everett M. Kassalow; Anthony Weinlein
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 425, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: John Brophy, fighter for industrial democracy, 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Report to the Industrial Union Department AFL-CIO, 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 3)
    Notes: th Constitutional Convention, Washington, D.C., November 16-17, 1961
  - Item 3: Summary report and conclusion of the IUD Seminar Collective Bargaining problems of Professional and Technical Workers in industry, 1960; Publication (Box 425, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Miscellaneous provisions of 13 professional and technical contracts, 1959; Publication (Box 425, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Factors affecting the development of labor movements abroad, 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 3)
    Notes: Two lectures - Part I-Western Movements, Part II-Unions in the New and Developing Countries
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Class bias in education, 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Labor and antitrust, 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Forsake me not, 1960; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
    Notes: Testimony of James B. Carey [as] secretary-treasurer [of the] Industrial Union Dept., AFL-CIO, before the Senate Subcommittee on Problems of the Aged and Aging, April 6, 1960. Second copy
  - Item 4: Problems of working women: summary report of a conference, 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Priorities for peace and survival, 1959; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Pills, prescriptions and profits., 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Industrial Union Department
  - Item 7: In your interest-the need for the "Truth in Lending" bill, 1965; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: A new program of free-world aid for the decade of development, 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Tent City, "home of the brave.", 1961; Publication (Box 425, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Keynote address to the fifth constitutional convention, 1963; Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Camouflage: the myth of "labor monopoly"., 1960; Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: What everyone should know about government spending and full employment, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The Civil rights fight: a look at the legislative record, 1960; Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Automation and major technological change: collective bargaining problems., 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
    Notes: Papers presented at a conference held .. April 22, 1958, Washington, D. C. 2 copies
  - Item 6: Automation and major technological change: impact on union size, structure and function., 1958; Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
    Notes: A panel discussion at a Conference held under the auspices of the Industrial Department AFL-CIO, April 22, 1958, Washington, D. C. 2 copies
  - Item 7: Industrial Unions and Taft-Hartley, 1960; Publication (Box 425, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Memorandum to All Users of IUD Economics Course Outline - Subject: Economics Course Outline, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Memo to University Labor Educators - Subject: Industrial Union Dept. Staff Education Program, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Class bias in education, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The margin of survival, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Automation's unkept promise, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: flyer-Fought any dragons lately?, Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: IUD Legislative Alert, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1962)
  - Item 8: Collective Bargaining Report, 1970; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1970)
  - Item 9: Planning and economic growth: a comparison between the US and other industrialized countries, 1962; Publication (Box 425, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: It's what's inside that counts, 1963; Publication (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Rules governing the extablishment and conduct of industrial union councils, 1963; Publication (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Mr. Farmer "Right to workers" are trying to--, Publication (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Agreement its a bargain!, Publication (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The American character, 1964; Publication (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Some questions and answers on the civil rights bill, 1963; Publication (Box 425, Folder 7)
    Author: Leadership Conference on Civil Rights
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: National Industrial Group Pension Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: America's health, 1965; Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: It's what's inside that counts, 1966; Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Some questions and answers on the civil rights bill, 1963; Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: American labor and world affairs: excerpts from convention resolutions and executive council statements, 1966; Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Justice, justice, shall ye pursue ..., 1964; Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
    Author: Nicholas deB. Katzenbach
  - Item 7: To meet the people's needs; statements adopted by the Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO, Executive Board., 1966; Publication (Box 426, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Your life is at stake, 1969; Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: IUD Information Center - Labor Day Edition (1968), Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: IUD Congressional Alert, 1968; Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Memo - To Presidents, Secretary-Treasurers, and Research Directors of IUD Affiliated Unions ---On Oct. 21 we sent you our computer analysis of 18 clauses found in our 100 major contract survey., 1969; Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Analysis 100 Major collective bargaining agreements, 1969; Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: IUD Data Center, 1969; Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Danger: men at work, 1969; Publication (Box 426, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1969 Occupational Safety and Health Conference of the Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO. 2 copies
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 426, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Memo - Dear Friend-In the few minutes it takes you to read this letter an American worker will be killed on his job and 148 others will be disabled by work accident or occupational illness., 1970; Publication (Box 426, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: IUD Spotlight on health and safety - v.1, no. 2, 1972; Publication (Box 426, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Needed: a constructive foreign trade policy, 1971; Publication (Box 426, Folder 3)
    Author: Stanley H. Ruttenberg & Associates
    Notes: A special study commissioned and published by the Industrial Union Dept., AFL-CIO, October 1971. 2 copies
  - Item 4: The developing crisis in international trade, 1970; Publication (Box 426, Folder 3)
    Author: I. W. Abel
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 426, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Case book; selected extracts from decisions of National Labor Relations Board and Courts., 1958; Publication (Box 426, Folder 4)
    Notes: Seminar on effects of NLRA upon Union activity.
  - Item 2: Staff training program, Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO: problems in arbitration, 1960; Publication (Box 426, Folder 4)
    Notes: Course for Union Staff Representatives
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Ever try to break a bunch of sticks?, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: It takes a big hammer to crack a tough nut, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Why coordinated bargaining?, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Coordinated bargaining means strength, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: IUD data Center, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Facts & Analysis Occupational health and Safety - no. 11, 1973; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Coordinated collective bargaining conference, 1973; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Proceedings of the IUD Coordinated Collective Bargaining Conference: January 10-11, 1973, Shoreham Hotel, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
    Author: IUD Coordinated Collective Bargaining Conference (1973: Washington, D.C.)
  - Item 9: The IUD program for retirement (flyer), 1973; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Putting it all together, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Coordinated bargaining: labor's new approach to effective contract negotiations, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The Stock option scandal, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Raw materials for America: a program to assure meeting future needs, 1975; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
    Author: Jocelyn Gutchess
  - Item 14: In UNITY there is strength!, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: No muscle, no money, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Coordinated bargaining is fair bargaining, 1977; Publication (Box 426, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 426, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The labor windows in Washington Cathedral, 1960-1969 (Box 426, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Pills, prescriptions and profits, 1961; Publication (Box 426, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Strike publicity guide for local unions, Publication (Box 426, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Religion and labor, Publication (Box 426, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Code key for identifying unions referred to by symbols, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Pumps and compressors industry: summary and statistical data, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Pumps and compressors industry, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Severance pay in key manufacturing agreements, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Wage increases provided in recent collective bargaining settlements -- Apr. 1, through June 6, 1958, Publication (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Wage increases provided in recent collective bargaining settlements -- Oct. through Dec. 1957, Publication (Box 427, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: What's lacking in labor education, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Wage increases provided in recent collective bargaining settlements -- Jan. thru Mar. 1958, Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Abstract of paper by Ted F. SilveyHuman factors in Automation, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Deferred wage increases to be effective in 1958 in manufacturing and selected non-manufacturing industries, Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Severance pay in key manufacturing agreements, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Survey of agreements in the pumps and compressors industry, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Arbitration experience under severance pay plans, 1959; Publication (Box 427, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 427, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Memo to Research Directors of All IUD Affiliates -- Subject: Recent Collective Bargainning Wage Settlements, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Comparison of selected provisions in 23 pumps and compressors industry contracts, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Holiday eligibility requirements and waivers contained in agreements of manufacturing companies with 5,000 or more workers, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Memo to Presidents and Research Directors of All IUD Affiliates -- Subject: Analysis of Holiday Pay Provisions in Key Manufacturing Agreements, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Vacations - number of weeks and length of service, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 427, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report to the Industrial Union Department AFL-CIO: 2nd Constitutional Convention, Washington, D.C., Oct. 31-Nov. 1, 1957, Publication (Box 427, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Memo to Presidents and Research Directors of All IUD Affiliates -- Subject: Analysis of Vacation Provisions in Large Manufacturing Agreements, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Affiliates of the Industrial Union Dept., 1956; Publication (Box 427, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Vacation -- eligibility requirements, 1958; Publication (Box 427, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 428, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: flyers - Organization your road to new frontiers on your job; Our stake in human rights; The compulsory arbitration fallacy, 1959; Publication (Box 428, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Analysis of Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 428, Folder 2)
    Author: Arthur J. Goldberg; Kenneth A. Meiklejohn
    Notes: Public Law 86-257, 86th Congress, 1st session, effective September 14, 1959
  - Item 3: Priorities for peace and survival, 1959; Publication (Box 428, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: A time for anger, 1959; Publication (Box 428, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Retirement and leisure in industrial society, 1959; Publication (Box 428, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Dear Fellow Citizen: In these pre-election days, the newspapers and airwaves are full of th sound and fury, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Memo To-Everett M. Kassalow -- Subject: Meeting with Key Non-Manual Workers Union Officials of the British TUC, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Memo To-Everett M. Kassalow -- Subject: Fifth and last in series of impressions of nonmanual unionism in Europe as seen during recent trip. White Collar Organization in Austria, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Memo To-Everett M. Kassalow -- Subject: Some impressions of White Collar Unionism in the Netherlands -- The NVV (Fourth in Series of Memos on my recent trip, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Memo To-Everett M. Kassalow -- Subject: Memorandum No. 3 on European Trip: Some aspects of the organization and operation of the DAG (Deutsche Angestellten-Gewerkschaft), independent German White Collar Workers' Union, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Summary report and conclusion of the IUD Seminar Collective Bargaining problems of Professional and Technical Workers in industry, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Collective bargaining problems of professional and technical workers, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: IUD Newsletter, 1969; Publication (Box 428, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (Nov. 1969)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 428, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Professional, technical and kindred workers by major industries, 1952-1959 (Box 428, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Total employment vs. production worker employment for selected industries, 1960; Publication (Box 428, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Text of the AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 428, Folder 4)
    Notes: Flyer. 2 copies, one photocopy.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 428, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: IUD Spotlight on health and safety - v.1, no. 1; v.2, no. 1-4; v.3, no. 1-2,4; v.4, no. 1, 1972-1975 (Box 428, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 429, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Resolution on immigration AFL-CIO convention - Dec. 1955, Publication (Box 429, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: American labor's interest in international affairs, 1959; Publication (Box 429, Folder 1)
    Author: George T. Brown
  - Item 3: Congreso de unidad AFL-CIO, 1959; Publication (Box 429, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO resolutions on international affairs, 1957; Publication (Box 429, Folder 1)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). International Affairs Dept.
    Notes: Adopted by the second Constitutional Convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, December, 1957.
  - Item 5: For world peace and freedom: proceedings, 1960; Publication (Box 429, Folder 1)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Conference on World Affairs (1960: New York)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Voice of America, Central program services division, features adaptation branch (this script is the property of the USA: it may not be used for commercial purposes and is subject to recall on demand), 1962; Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO Free Trade Union News, 1966; Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1966)
  - Item 3: AFL-CIO Free Trade Union News, 1970; Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.25:no.5 (1970)
  - Item 4: Statement by the AFL-CIO Executive Council on International Trade Policy, 1961; Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Washington reports to the people -- Subject: Foreign Aid Proving a success, 1963; Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The AFL-CIO's foreign policy, 1987; Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The AFL-CIO abroad: perspectives on labor and the world, 1987; Publication (Box 429, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 429, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Publicity handbook - Joint Minimum Wage Committee, AFL-CIO, 1959; Publication (Box 429, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The people America can't forget: the case for a better minimum wage law., 1957; Publication (Box 429, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Six wage-hour stories from: 'The people directly involved.', 1959; Publication (Box 429, Folder 3)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Joint Minimum Wage Committee
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 429, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the Joint AFL-CIO Unity Committee to the first constitutional convention, 1955; Publication (Box 429, Folder 4)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Joint Unity Committee
  - Item 2: Resolution on the achievement of labor unity, 1955; Publication (Box 429, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 429, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Investment of union pension funds, 1980; Publication (Box 429, Folder 5)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Committee on the Investment of Union Pension Funds